A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
- Henry, Harold Lionel, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Henry, May, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Henry, Ruth, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Henry, Timothy Edgar, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Herbert, Thomas Swepston, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Herd, Margaret M., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Hernaman, Sarah Leolia, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Herndon, Brodie S., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Herndon, Frost Hiram, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Herring, Alvah Livingston, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Herring, Lena Rollings, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Herring, Susan Darracott, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Hersman, Grace, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Hersman, Howard Johnston, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Hervey, Lucille Cullingworth, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Heslep, Charles Fraser, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Hess, John Frances, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Hess, Walter, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Hester, George Franklin, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hewitt, Elizabeth Brock, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hewitt, Ethel Willis, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Hewitt, Irene M., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Hewitt, Jean Curd, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hewitt, Marion Stetson, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hewlett, Mary Cooke, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Heximer, Earnest Edgar, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Heystik, [infant], 1943 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Hibble, Charles Eddie, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Hickmon, John Vernon, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Hickok, Belle Hambleton, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hicks, Emma K., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hicks, Jean Wilkie, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Hicks, Sallie Elizabeth, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hicks, Spiller, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Higginbotham, Elmslie G., Jr., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Higginbotham, Mary, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Higgins, Allie Knotts, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Higgins, Elsie H. L., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Higgins, Marie Brown, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Higgins, Robert Barnard, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Higgins, Roswell Linton, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Higgins, William H., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- High, George Thomas, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Higinbotham, Harlow Niles, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hilferty, Edward F., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Hilgeman, Donald Parker [infant], 1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Hill, Allan Christian, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hill, Bessie, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Hill, Bessie Powell, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Hill, Carlotta Mallory, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Hill, Carrie Archer, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Hill, Clara Viola, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Hill, Cora Bransford, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hill, Elizabeth Palmer, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hill, Emma Gill, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hill, Emory, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hill, Ezekial Thomas, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Hill, Frank Deane, Jr., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Hill, Franklin Stanhop, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hill, Gwendolyn, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Hill, Hazel, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Hill, Isabel S., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hill, James Hartwell, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Hill, James L., Jr., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Hill, Katharine Ingles, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Hill, Lelia Palmer, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hill, Mary Eva Templeton, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Hill, Mary Frances, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hill, Nannie Massie, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hill, Viada Dumond, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Hill, William E., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hill, William Palmer, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hilliard, Eulalia Spindle, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hilliard, Lula Trice, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hillsman, John Mitchell, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Hillsman, Lavinia B., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Hillsman, Lavinia Burwell, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Hillsman, Rose Lindner, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Hiner, Kenneth Robert, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Hines, [infant], 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Hines, Clarissa Penn, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Hines, Lucy Catherine, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hinkle, Christine Smith, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Hinton, Elizabeth Reed, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hinton, George Henry, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Hinton, John R., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Hinton, Mabel C., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Hinton, Nannie Sledd, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hirshberg, Julia A., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hitch, Clyde B., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hite, Cornelius Baldwin, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hitt, Mamie Luthenia, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Hoag, Anna Tichnor, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hobart, Gertrude Bensley, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Hobart, John Edgar, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hobart, Wilbur Faxon, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Hobbs, William Randolph, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Hobson, Alex Trent, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hobson, Annie Camp, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Hobson, Annie Leigh Camm, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hobson, Bessie Martin H., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Hobson, Edwin Lafayette, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Hobson, Elizabeth Bridges, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Hobson, Elizabeth Doswell, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Hobson, Elizabeth Graham Bruce, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Hobson, Ellen Graham, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Hobson, Fannie A., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Hobson, Fannie Anderson, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hobson, Frank A., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hobson, Frank Archer, Jr., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hobson, Graham B., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hobson, John Cannon, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Hobson, John S., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hobson, Joseph Reid Anderson, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hobson, Mariane Gertrude, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hobson, Mary Binford, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hobson, Matthew deGraffenreidt, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hobson, Robert Archer, 1960 (disinterred 1976) (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Hobson, Sally Archer Anderson, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Hobson, Sarah Weisiger, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hobson, Saunders, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hobson, William Plummer, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hockett, Lillie Perkins, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hodder, Alice Crosby, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Hodgers, Clifton, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Hodges, Charles C., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Hodges, Charles Christopher, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Hodges, Leroy Sherrill, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hodges, Lucy, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hodges, William Jesse, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Hodkinson, Sydney Jack, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Hoff, Ebbe Curtis, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Hoff, Margaret Jones, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Hoffman, Augusta Marie, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hoffman, Travis F., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Hogan, Carolyn Tubb, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Hogan, Margaret Rosalind, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hogan, Virginia Rives Rowe, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Hoge, Edmund H., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Hoge, Frances Jones, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Hoge, Howard Dandridge, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hoge, Jessie Evans, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Hogeboom, Herbert Franklin, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hoggan, Nelle Large, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Hoggard, J. T. (George), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Hogge, Mary Fitzgerald, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Hogge, Mosby, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Holderness, George Allen, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Holdsworth, George D., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Holladay, Addison Lewis, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Holladay, Caroline Gwathmey, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Holladay, James Rawlins, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Holladay, Juliet Biggers, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Holland, Bernard P., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Holland, Ralph, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Hollingsworth, Louise B., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Hollingsworth, Russell, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Holloway, Margaret Sedgwick, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Holman, Charles Allen, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Holman, Evelyn Conrad, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Holman, Maria Evans, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Holman, William Miller, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Holmes, Earl E., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Holmes, Frank Aguster, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Holmes, Henry Benjamin, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Holmes, Justin Brown, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Holms, Alice Savage, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Holobaugh, Charles Franklin, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Holt, Branch Thomas Hollingsworth, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Holt, Henry Winston, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Holt, Josephine White, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Holt, Mary Mason Williams, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Holtzclaw, Estelle Grigg, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Holtzclaw, Jack Gilbert, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Holtzclaw, Lucy Lee, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Holtzclaw, Murray Baldwin, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Holzapfel, Daisy, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Holzbach, Katie, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Hood, Kent William, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Hood, Martha Jarvis, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Hood, William T., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hoofnagle, [infant], 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Hoofnagle, Katherine C., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Hooker, Bettie Tyson, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Hooker, Josephine Teresa H., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Hoover, Dorothy Anne, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Hopkins, Bessie J., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Hopkins, Charles F., Jr., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hopkins, Charles William, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hopkins, James Alfred, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hopkins, Jeb Stuart, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Hopkins, Mary, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Hopkins, Mary S., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Hopp, Jessie Harriet, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Hopper, Robert, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Hopper, Thomas Bradford, Jr., 1983 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Hord, Harry, Jr., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Horner, Everett T., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Horner, Maude Pierce, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Horsely, Catherine W., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Horsley, Lillian Holladay, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Horton, Esther Landrum, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Horton, William D., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Hoster, Sally Eddy, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Hotchkiss, Alice Starke, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hotchkiss, Bryan, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Hotchkiss, Elizabeth A., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Hotchkiss, Elmore Delos, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hotchkiss, Henry Starke, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Hotchkiss, Jedediah Grant, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Hotchkiss, Lilian A., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Hotchkiss, Nelson Hill, Jr., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Hotchkiss, Ruth V., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Houchens, Newell Hamilton, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Houchens, Sarah Virginia Newell, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Hough, J. Malcolm, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Hough, Wilbur S., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Houghton, Clara Elizabeth, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Houpe, Lacy Rockwell, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Houston, Charles F., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Houston, Elizabeth Price, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Houston, Elizabeth Price, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Houston, Janet Carolyn, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Houston, Olive Amelia, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Houston, Stella Margaret, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Hovey, John Jacobs, Jr., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Hovey, Marguerite Haynes, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hovis, Harriet McKean, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Howard, Anastasia, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Howard, Conway Robertson, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Howard, Edward T. C., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Howard, Jeannie Colston, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Howard, John, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Howard, Mary Catherine, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Howard, Mary Frances, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Howard, Mary MacLeod, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Howard, Theodore C., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Howard, Thomas L., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Howard, Virginia Binford, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Howard, William Orlando, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Howard, William Rodney, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Howe, Ethel C., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Howe, Harriet Campbell, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Howell, Ardon, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Howell, Clara Jackson, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Howell, Elizabeth H., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Howell, George, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Howell, Joseph Adams, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Howell, Madge Virginia, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Howell, Mary Gentry, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Howell, Muriel Johnson, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Howell, Thomas B., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Howerton, Loulie LaFon, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Howle, Adeline Green, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Howle, Paul W., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Howlett, Page Pelham, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Huband, Arthur Lee, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Huband, Susie Mae Williams, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Hubard, Helen Harrison, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Hubard, Nathaniel Walter, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hubbard, Emerline Senorale, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Hubbard, Emma Nimo, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hubbard, John, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Hubbard, Louise Carrington, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Hubbard, Martha Ann, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Hubbard, Mary H., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hubbard, Miles Falkiner, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Hubbard, Sarah L. Saunders, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hubbard, Sarah Waddill, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hudgins, Gilbert Lee, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hudgins, R. Lester, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hudgins, Sarah Jane, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hudgins, William Jesse, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Hudson, Irving Wise, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hudson, Joseph, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Hudson, Luke Floyd, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Hudson, Octavia Pender, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Huey, Charlotte Johnson, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Huff, Clayton Charles, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hughes, Cadwalder Owen, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hughes, Capitola Luttrell, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hughes, Charles Brock, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Hughes, Christopher Miller, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Hughes, Dorothy Dame, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Hughes, Edward Everett, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hughes, Emily Johnson, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Hughes, Evelyn Ryce, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Hughes, Jennie Anne, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hughes, Marion Mahone, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Hughson, Judith Crawford, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hulce, Hannah Marie, n. d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Hulcher, Julius Joseph, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Hull, Joseph Kelly, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hull, Maude Pollard, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Hull, Vernon Lee, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Hullihen, Elizabeth C., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Hume, Bryce Stewart, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hume, Graham Watkins, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hume, James, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Hume, Katherine Beach, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Hume, Louise C., 1975 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Hummel, Frances Hayden, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Hummel, Fred Edgar, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Hummel, John Peter, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hummel, Maria Jones, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Hump, Helen, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hundley, Edi Lee Murray, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Hundley, Harold Scott, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Hunt, Cora R., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Hunt, Emile Klein, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Hunt, John Leigh, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Hunt, Kate, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hunt, Katherine Coleman Johnston, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hunt, Love Finney, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hunt, William Oliver, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Hunter, Anne Pendleton, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Hunter, Charles Wesley, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hunter, Emily Mary, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Hunter, Ethel May, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Hunter, Gabriella Browne, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Hunter, Hallie Sutton, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Hunter, Imogen Riddick, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hunter, James Duncan, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Hunter, Jennie Winston Cooke, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Hunter, Josie Daniel, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hunter, Louise B., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Hunter, Mattie F., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hunter, Mildred VanCleave, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Hunter, Morris, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Hunter, Parthenia, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hunter, Pauline Elliott, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hunter, Richard, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hunter, Robert Tucker, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Huntington, Frederick, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Huntley, Elizabeth Frances, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Huntley, Katherine G., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Huntley, Wesley P., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Huntley, William Woodson, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Hunton, Caroline Marye, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Hunton, Eppa, IV, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Hunton, Eppa, Jr., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Hunton, Virginia P., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Huntt, Edward, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Huntt, George Hathaway, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Huntzinger, Beulah C., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Hurd, Albert R., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Hurd, Ebenezer, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Hurd, Evmarhel Ruth Jones, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Hurd, Wilhelmina, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Hurt, Algernon Smith, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Hurt, Algernon Smith, Jr., 1982 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Hurt, Charles Clyde, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hurt, Eleanor A., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Hurt, Eugene Stanley, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Hurt, Herbert Linwood, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Hurt, Julia McRae, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hurt, Mary Elizabeth Wilson, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Hurt, Robert Hayward, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Hurtt, Charles Dunton, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Hurtt, Louise Trail Woodward, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Huss, John Wesley, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Husten, George Thomas, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Hutcherson, Hazel Newcomb, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Hutcheson, Bessie Price, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Hutcheson, Ella B., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Hutcheson, Erskine Miller, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Hutcheson, James Morrison, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Hutcheson, James Morrison, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Hutcheson, Margaret Erskine, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Hutcheson, Nellie Lewis, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Hutcheson, Sarah Ann, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Hutchins, Virginia Rheutan, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Hutchinson, Elizabeth Dougall, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Hutchinson, Lelia, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Hutchinson, Lucinda, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hutchinson, Susan Amanda, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hutchison, Robert Richard, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Hutton, Lillian V., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Huxter, Elizabeth Christian, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Huxter, Walker Lee Christian, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Huxter, William, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Huyett, Bessie C., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Huylett, Charles Benjamin, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Hyde, Mabel Taylor, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Inge, Norman Jones, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Ingles, Elizabeth Robinson, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Ingles, Harriette Greenway, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Ingram, Eleanor M., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Ingram, Ellen Douglas, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Ingram, Elsie Page, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Ingram, Herschel Anthony, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Ingram, John Littlepage, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Ingram, Octavia Page Sublett, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Ingram, Phyllis Newby, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Ingram, Virginia Hunter, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Irby, Paul Burdett, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Irby, William Logan, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Iredell, Roberta Edmond, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Ireland, Alice, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Irvin, Amanda Virginia, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Irvine, Ellanita Allen, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Irvine, Phillip C., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Irvine, Roberta Nolting, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Irwin, Lucy Haines, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Isaacs, Minnie Monteiro, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Isabell, John Henry, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Isbell, Grace, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Isbell, John Henry, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Isbell, Robert Jefferson, Jr., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Isbell, William M., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Iseman, Ruth T., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Iverson, Jacqueline Lamb, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Ivey, Alphonso Lynn, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Izard, Ralph, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Izzard, Retta Lyons, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Jackson, Amy Sue, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Jackson, Annie Philips, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Jackson, Bessie Melville, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Jackson, Eleanora Nash, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Jackson, Eugenia, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Jackson, Evelyn Hyman, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Jackson, Everett Palmer, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Jackson, George Alexander, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Jackson, George Carlton, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jackson, Helen Turnbull, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Jackson, Herbert W., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Jackson, Herbert W., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Jackson, Josephine Rose, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Jackson, Margaret Louise Garrett, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Jackson, Marguerite, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Jackson, Martha, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Jackson, Mary Elizabeth Jeffress, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Jackson, May Elizabeth, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Jackson, Nannie Woolfolk Samuel, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Jacob, John Franklin, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Jacob, Nettie Clay, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Jacob, Nettie Sneed, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Jacobs, Annie Virginia, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Jacobs, Bernard Marshall, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Jacobs, Frank Boykin, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jacobs, Irving Nash, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Jamerson, Elsie Tower, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Jamerson, George H., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Jamerson, Osmond, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- James, Algernon Sidney Buford, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- James, Andrew Ellerson, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- James, Bertrand T., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- James, Florence Virginia, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- James, Jack R., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- James, Mary Elizabeth, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- James, Mary Elizabeth, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- James, Mary Garnett, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- James, Matthew F., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- James, Orlo B., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- James, William A., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- James, William A., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Jameson, Sarah Jane, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Jamieson, Harriet Barber, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Jamieson, John, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Jamison, Ada Clough, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Jamison, Arthur Wellington, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Janney, Lucy Bosher, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Jarvis, Laura Morris, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Jefferies, Adeline Harris, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Jefferies, Richard Henry, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Jefferson, [infant], 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jefferson, George C., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Jefferson, Sarah M., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Jeffery, Richard W., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Jeffress, Arthur Tilden (3 folders), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Jeffress, Elizabeth Gwathmey, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Jeffress, Jenny W., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Jeffress, Kate Miller, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Jeffress, Robert Miller, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Jeffress, Thomas Fox, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jeffreys, Robert Massey, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Jeffries, Lucy Harper, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jeffries, Thomas Tabb, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Jeffries, William Ladson, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Jenkins, [infant] of Roy, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Jenkins, Addie Abner, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Jenkins, Edward Thomas, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Jenkins, Ella O., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Jenkins, Emma Jane, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jenkins, Emma V., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Jenkins, John W., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Jenkins, Jonathan Warren, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)